<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<name>Celsius</name>
	<author>Garwel</author>
	<url>https://github.com/GarwelGarwel/Celsius</url>
	<packageId>Garwel.Celsius</packageId>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.3</li>
		<li>1.4</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<description>Celsius adds realistic simulation of thermodynamics to the game.

Main features:

- Temperature is tracked and accurately represented for every map cell (loosely) based on real-world thermal properties.

- Water can freeze and ice can melt.

- Flammable things may spontaneously ignite when it gets extremely hot.

Celsius opens up many new challenges and ways to play RimWorld. Forgo houses and warm colonists at campfires, melt ice sheets or unleash deadly firestorms on your enemies!

Some vanilla shortcuts and assumptions have been removed, which affected balance of many things (e.g. the size of rooms heated by a firplace).

I worked hard to optimize the mod, and it shouldn't seriously slow down the game. You may disable or tweak its features to your liking.

You can install it in an ongoing game. Removal mid-game is also theoretically possible but untested.

DLCs are supported. Mods support is an ongoing effort. Mod authors can provide patches on their side or submit PRs in Github.

For issue reports, suggestions and pull requests, visit Github: https://github.com/GarwelGarwel/Celsius

Dependencies:
- Harmony
- XML Extensions

Currently supported mods:
- Insulation
- Primitive Workbenches
- Vanilla Furniture Extended: base mod, Architect, Medical, Security
- Windows

Conflicts:
- Any mod that alters temperature-related things in the game is likely to cause issues. 
- Heat Map, Proxy Heat are not needed, because Celsius does everything these mod do (and much more)</description>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>imranfish.xmlextensions</packageId>
			<displayName>XML Extensions</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2574315206</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/15adhami/XmlExtensions/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>imranfish.xmlextensions</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>
